<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OnmyojiInfomation</string>
    <string name="youtouhime">Did you see that...? Whenever dangers nearby I end up like that... I turn into this demon sword, this weapon. Terrifying, right...? If you are strong, you will hurt others.</string>
    <string name="ibarakidouji">Six realms of Existence, all creature were only a drop in the ocean in this world, even the monsters. Once relaxed, then will be bullied by others, played, and even killed. So they must have a leader to guide them. To survive in this world of jungle is law, prostrated under the strong!</string>
    <string name="flower">Oh, whats up, do you want to hear my story? Are you sure? You might have the consciousness for that, didnot you? If you want to hear strange stories, then you should prepare to hear until the sunrise. I love strange stories, whether if it is said to people, or to hear by people</string>
    <string name="shutendouji">They say that alcohol is the worst poison,but I dont think so. To me,alcohol is the best medicine. As soon as you drink with someone, you can see their true nature. Just look at everyone who doesnt drink, how boring are they? Is that bitch Enma still in the other world? She can sure stand such a boring place. Is that idiot Ootengu still chasing the fool around? Serves him right.</string>
    <string name="otengu">Ōtengu appears as a handsome man with short pale blond hair and blue eyes. A large pair of black wings grow from his back. He wears a white sokutai with blue swirling patterns at the front panel, shoulders and sleeves, with a red tassel hanging from the hem of each sleeve. There is a red demon mask with long white moustache situated at the front of the belt. He also dons a pair of black trousers, white socks and steel blue geta sandals. He carries a blue uchiwa fan with two red tassels hanging from the edge and the kanji 祭 (matsuri, festival) written on both sides</string>
    <string name="enma">My Yama temple, it is really a boring place. There are just a pair of unreliable brothers, a strange stockpot, and an iceberg. The brothers only have each other in their eyes. The stockpot was bullied by me, I cant even find her.</string>
</resources>
